我忘记拿了
I forgot them.
我要你给我送过来
Now,I need you to bring me some.
你的备用裤子呢?
What about your spare pants?
上周四的芥末事件
Last Thursday, the mustard incident.
天哪 你真是个金鱼脑袋\n(金鱼的记忆只有3秒)
Jeez,woman,you have the\nmemory of a goldfish.
不 Ted 你那事绝不会那么简单
No,Ted,you're not getting off that easy.
Marshall的裤子糗事 还有点笑料...
Marshall's pants story, while amusing...
才有点笑料? 是笑爆掉吧
Amusing? Try very amusing.
比起Karen的事 这根本不值一提\n先把你的故事讲完
Is nothing compared to this\nKaren madness. Finish your story.
咋了? 就这些\n只是在餐馆里啵了下而已
What? That's it. It was just\none kiss in the restaurant.
为啥特地指明"在餐馆里"
Why did you say "in the restaurant?"
你们还在哪里啵了?
Did you kiss somewhere else?
譬如说 在树上?
Like where,in a tree?
没 Lily 我们可没在树上干
No,Lily,we did not make out in a tree.